TABINDA NOOR

Web Developer

BASIC INFORMATION

Muhallah Mustafabad Faisalabad tabindanoor415@gmail.com, +92 3055734382

Date of birth: March 21, 2002

Website: linkedin.com/in/tabinda-noor-935429237

Github: https://github.com/Tabindanoor

SUMMARY

Front end developer for designing and implementing the user interface of a website or application. Passionate in learning new skills and having interest for technology. Experienced with over 2 year of experience in Industry and 4 years in personal. Good reputation for resolving problems. Efficient professional with a self-motivated nature.

Certified Ethical hacker with skills in Kali Linux OS and networking.

My objective is to secure a challenging position in a reputable organization to expand my learnings, knowledge, and skills and aim to venture new areas and work in a stable organization with a dynamic environment to work in an organization that has a room for self-development and growth.

EDUCATION

01-10-2020 - 01-10-2024

Government College University Faisalabad 3.75 CGPA

May 2018 - June 2020 **ICS**

Kips College jail Road Faisalabad

Matriculation April 2016 - April 2018

Govt. Muslim Girls High School 94 %

SKILLS

- Git/GitHub
- C++
- OOP
- HTML5
- CSS
- Tailwind CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- TypeScript

This resume is made with CVwizard.com.

- React.js
- Redux / Redux-Toolkit
- MUI
- Firebase
- Node JS
- Express JS
- Mongo DB
- Python
- MSSQL
- · Ethical hacking
- MS Office
- CCNA
- PHP

CERTIFICATIONS

- JavaScript By Coursera
- MERN Bootcamp
- Testing with Selenium 3 months Training
- Computer Networking Workshop
- Cyber Security
- NSE-1 (Network Security Associate)
- NSE-2 (Network Security Associate)
- HCIA SECURITY
- HCIA CLOUD COMPUTING
- Programming Quiz competition in GCUF

WORK EXPERIENCE

Programmmer

Corvit Systems Faisalabad

- Worked in python programming Language
- Manage the instances of AWS using python scripts
- Collaboration with the team to fulfil cloud based tasks

MERN Bootcamper

02-20-2023 - 24-08-2023

Techloset Solutions

- Designing and implementing user interfaces for websites or web applications.
- Writing clean, efficient, and maintainable code using HTML, CSS, and React JS along with the Tailwind CSS.
- Optimizing web pages for maximum speed and scalability.
- Testing and debugging front-end code to identify and fix any issues or bugs
- Ensuring cross-browser compatibility and responsiveness of websites
- Keeping up-to-date with the latest web development trends and technologies

Web Developer Instructor

25-08-2022 - 01-02-2023

ITEC Systems Faisalabad

With the experience as a web instructor, I have gained invaluable insights into the art of guiding and educating aspiring web developers. During this time, I have had the privilege of instructing students from diverse backgrounds, each with their unique learning needs.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

- Scientific calculator in C++
- Course management system in Java
- Library management system in Java
- PHP scraping for car comparison website
- Hotel management system in ASP.net
- Mobile Repair Shop in .net
- Deep face Detection in python using tensorflow
- Alexedria Landing page in React
- Bash Scripting In Kali Linux for Information Gathering Tools
- E-Learning Web App in React
- Todo List in react with firebase Authentication
- My Portfolio in React
- Flipkart Clone in MERN
- Small Gallery App in MERN
- Hotel Management System in C++

INTERESTS

- MERN Stack
- Web Development
- Android Development
- Programming Languages
- Ethical Hacking

LANGUAGES	
English	Urdu
Punjabi	
QUALITIES	
■ Effective Communication	■ LeaderShip
■ Management	■ Problem Solving